Subtitle : ByME
We are now closer
than we have ever been.
We are now closer than we have ever been.
To victory.
Some... Some are already
calling it the greatest.
Some are already calling it
the greatest victory in
the history of mankind.
Some are calling it already.
We are closer than we
have ever been to victory.
Some are already
calling it the greatest
victory in the history
of military campaigns.
Today I can announce that the so called
western forces of Texas and California
have suffered a very great
loss, a very great defeat
at the hands of the fighting men and women
of the United States military.
The people of Texas and California
should know that they will be welcomed
back to these United States
as soon as their illegal
secessionist government is deposed.
I can also confirm that the Florida
alliance has failed in its attempt to
force the brave people of the
Carolinas into joining the insurrection.
Citizens of America, we are now
closer than ever to a historic victory
as we eliminate the final
pockets of resistance.
God bless you all and God bless America.
you okay?
- What?
- You're Lee Smith.
This is crazy.
- Take this.
- No. I can't do that
Take it and put it on.
Thank you so much.
We woke up in Des Moines, Iowa,
and he's wearing my wedding ring.
Jesus, the wifi is fucking slow.
The word I'm getting is July 4.
The word you're getting?
Like everyone in this room hasn't already
heard this bullshit.
The life force and the
optics are irresistable.
The western forces are
stopped 120 miles from the sea.
The Florida alliance
armed for south of them.
The WF one had stopped. They
stalled and lost their supply lines.
But it's the race to Berlin.
There's no coordination
between the secessionists.
You watch.
As soon as DC falls,
they'll turn on each other.
- Really?
- It's every night this week.
They'll switch to the generator.
Uploaded.
Almost done.
So where you kids headed tomorrow?
Staying in New York a while
or adventuring out?
- Fuck you.
- Come on, Jim.
So you can beat us there?
I couldn't beat you in a brisk walk.
We're going there,
we're going to DC,
Danny.
Tomorrow morning, first thing.
Yeah, front line. I figured.
No, no, not at the front line.
DC.
- What?
- I'm gonna photograph the president.
Joe's gonna interview.
Photograph and interview the
president in DC.
That's the idea.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Are you serious?
They shoot journalists
on site in the Capitol.
They literally see us as enemy
combatants.
Not a single interview in
14 months.
Now how you gonna do this?
We get there before anyone else does.
You think there's a rush?
To get executed on the south lawn.
Same. July 4, July 10. West coast forces.
Fucking Portland Maoists.
It's all the same.
DC is falling and the president is dead
inside the mouth.
Interviewing is the only story left.
It's not a story if
it never gets filed.
Lee, can I please talk you
out of this bullshit?
What do you think the
route's gonna be like?
There's nothing direct, the interstates are
vaporized,
and you can't get anywhere near Philly.
So you gotta go west.
Maybe as far as Pittsburgh,
then circle in from West Virginia.
You already had that route
all figured out, huh, Sammy?
Yeah, okay. I was kind of
looking to get down there myself.
- I knew it
- Not DC.
I don't want a piece of your suicide pact.
I want Charlottesville front line.
- Sammy
- Hear me out.
Just cause I'm a rival news out.
They're not a fucking vice.
You think I care if you fight with
whatever's left of the New York Times?
You're worried I'm too old,
I can't move quick enough.
Aren't you? Sure,
yes. But you
gonna make me explain
why I have to be there
it's the front line, you want,
half the press in this room are gonna
be heading there within 24 hours.
You want me to walk
around this fucking room
begging for a ride?
I'm gonna finish the upload
upstairs and pass out.
Hopefully we'll be done
by the time I wake up.
My vote. If Sammy wants a ride, I'm good
with it.
You two figure it out.
Thank you, Lee.
Yeah, thank you, Lee.
Make me the bad guy.
Ma'am, just to warn you,
if you take the elevator, we
do sometimes have power cuts,
which might mean a delay
in your journey.
A delay?
We offer the option to use the stairs.
I'm on the 10th floor.
Your choice, ma'am.
Miss Smith? Hey,
it's me. Do you remember me earlier?
Yeah, how did you know I stay...
Yeah, I didn't mean to, like, stalk,
but I know a lot of
the press use this hotel
and I wanted to say thanks.
And I want to give you this back.
Oh, no, it's okay. Keep it.
- But,
- keep it.
And buy a helmet and some Kevlar. Okay.
If you're planning on attending any more
stuff like that.
I am. Yeah, going to. I'm a photographer.
And I want to be a war photographer.
Actually.
By the way, you have the
same name as my hero,
Lee Miller.
She was one of the first
photojournalists in knockout.
You know her stuff.
Yeah, I know who Lee Miller is.
Of course. But I want to say
that you're also one of my heroes.
And you've got the same
name too.
Well, thank you.
I'm in good company.
What's your name?
Jesse.
Jessie Cullen.
So, Jesse, I've gotta walk up ten flights
of stairs,
but if I ever see you again,
you better be wearing Kevlar and that's vest.
You bet.
A word? What the fuck is that girl doing?
Right, so she came over to the
table last night after you went to bed.
She's very cool and wanted to tag along,
so she's coming with us.
Lee, you let Sammy tag along?
You think he's gonna
do well running for cover
with bullets flying over his head?
She's a kid, did you notice that?
She's like 23 and
she wants to do what we do.
She wants to do what you do.
We had to start one day.
Were you more children than
she? She is now.
Whatever happens, she goes
no further than Charlottesville.
All right, let's go.
You don't want to miss this.
Mister President, do you regret any action
implemented during
your third term in office?
I'm not gonna softball him, Sammy.
In retrospect, Mister president, do you
still think it was wise to disband the FBI?
Passive aggressive.
Sir, how is your policy evolving in the use
of airstrikes against american citizens?
Now we're talking.
Just be sure you get the words out
before the piano wire gets too tight.
There's a gas station station up ahead.
Looks open.
I've got over half a tank.
What do you think?
Any chance to refuel.
We should take.
Ok.
- Can I help you folks?
- Just looking for gas.
Got a local fuel permit?
No, we're actually
just passing through.
Can't help. Sorry.
Sir, we pay.
I was never gonna give it for free.
- Over the odds.
- What's over the odds?
300 for
half a tank and two cans.
300 buys you a sandwich.
We got ham or
cheese.
300 canadian.
Okay.
Hey. Stretching the legs?
No, I just saw
something.
This isn't going to take long.
Sure.
- Are we good?
- Yeah, we're good.
I don't mind if she looks.
- Who are they?
- Looters.
Actually not that guy went to high school
together.
Didn't talk to me much.
We just want to
talk to him now.
We've been debating
what to do with him
for two days now.
Go around in circles.
Tell you what,
why don't you put us and them
out of our misery and make a call?
I'll put rounds in them right now.
Or we'll beat them up a little more.
Strap them to the front.
We'll let them go after a couple days.
Flip a coin if you like.
Would you stand with that?
Yeah.
I'd like to take your picture.
Okay. You stand over there.
Yeah. Where you want me to do?
Uh, between the two.
I didn't take a photo.
I didn't take a single photo.
I didn't even remember.
I have cameras on me,
like. Oh, my God.
Like. Like, why didn't I
just tell him not to shoot?
They're probably gonna kill that manual.
How do you know?
He doesn't know. But that's besides the
point.
Once you start asking
yourself those questions,
You can't stop.
So we don't ask. We record.
So other people ask.
Want to be a journalist? That's the
job.
Hey, Lee.
- What?
- Back off.
What am I saying that's wrong?
I'm not saying it's wrong.
she just shook up.
Lee doesn't understand shook up.
Whoa.
I'm not being protective of her.
You're the idiot who let her in
this car.
What happened back there is nothing
in comparison to what we're heading into.
You need to understand.
Holy shit.
She's the back seat. It's both in
kindergarden and an old child's home.
How did this happen?
Lee, what the fuck?
She's right.
I won't make that mistake again
terms of the so called peace summit
could only be rejected,
fully rejected, by all.
To the secessionists, I say only this.
I pledge allegiance to the flag
of the United States of America.
We stand ready to fulfill the
promise of our forefathers.
To the flag, to the nation,
and to God.
Stop here a minute.
Like a good place
for a toilet break.
Just pull it.
Come with me.
Shoot it.
Shoot the helicopter?
Yeah. It's gonna
make a good image.
That V2. You don't see
them around much.
Yeah, they're my dad's cameras, actually.
Don't worry. He's not dead.
He's sitting on his farm in Missouri
pretending like none of this is happening.
Lee, I'm sorry for jamming
my way into your ride, okay?
I know you're really angry about it.
And I know you think
I don't know shit, but...
I'm not angry about that. Jesse.
I don't care what you do or don't
know.
Okay? But you are angry with me.
There is no version of this
that isn't a mistake.
I know because I'm it.
Joe and Sammy are it.
- It's my choice,
- Right.
And I'll remember that
when you lose your shit
or you get blown up or shot.
Would you photograph that moment?
If I got shot?
What do you think.
Every time I survived the
war zone and got the photo,
I thought I was sending a
warning, home.
Don't do this.
But here we are.
- So it's existential.
- What is?
What's eating you?
Don't worry about me, Sammy.
Am I allowed to say
I remember you at her age,
and I wasn't so different?
- You weren't so different.
You think you're being hard on her,
and I think you're being hard on yourself.
Okay, Ryder.
Damn it, Lee,
Stop. I'm speaking truth.
And for the record, sure,
I'm worried about that girl.
And I'm worried about you, too.
What are you worrying about Lee for?
Lee's lost her faith in
the power of journalism.
State of the nation is QED.
I can't answer to that, Sammy.
But I can tell you this gunfire is
getting extremely fucking hard.
Look at that shit.
Light up this guy.
It's not our story.
Yeah, but, you know,
bang, bang.
We're not going anywhere near that in
the dark.
But, Senna,
they're still at it.
We'll take a look.
Cool.
Thanks.
Action tomorrow.
We going down there?
Yeah.
But not you.
You're gonna hang back.
I don't want to hang back.
You have to hanging back.
I'm not hanging back.
You should see your face.
Stomach don't turn right,
you don't get a minute of sleep tonight.
My advice, don't expect to sleep
That way, if you do it,
it's a nice surprise.
You gonna sleep?
I got out a bit adequate.
I know. It's okay.
Or I can stay up with you,
keep you company.
No, I don't want to be
a burden or whatever.
Sure
But seriously, if you do get
freaked out or something,
just wake me up. It's not nice being
scared alone.
Thanks, Joe.
You better
Get ready to move out of here.
Fuck smoke.
Hang in.
Give me that.
What a fucking rush.
- Yes, ma'am.
- Id's?
Okay. Are you staying the night?
Yeah, just one
Park over there.
There's a canteen where you can eat
and no tents available.
Thanks, maam.
Yeah.
- I brought you something. - Thanks.
- Don't forget to eat.
- I'm starving.
Eat.
Once I'm done with this
Developing right on the road.
Yeah,
I got myself a pretty neat travel kit.
I'm impressed.
Want to know the secret of getting
the developer just right?
Body temperature.
- Smart.
- Thank you.
So, how about you tell me the story of
how you became photojournalists?
You don't know.
I thought I was one of your heroes.
Yeah, I do.
When you were in college,
you took the motherfucking
legendary photo of the antifa massacre.
Then you became the youngest
ever Madden photographer.
That would be my Wikipedia page.
But what's missing from it?
I don't know, Cloud.
Well, that's gotta sit
here for ten minutes,
so you might as well expand
a little.
What about your folks?
Well, actually, they're on a farm too.
Oh, except Colorado. Also pretending
this isn't happening.
No shit.
Hey, these are dry.
Should we check them out?
Sure.
Still need a phone even
though you can't get a signal.
I don't want you to see these.
Um, they're not even in focus.
Like exposure's all wrong.
Keep looking. I figure the strike
rate for keepers is 30 to one.
It's a great photo, Jesse.
Did we just drive through a time portal?
It's a twilight zone.
Hey there. Welcome.
Feel free to look around.
Hey, out of interest,
are you guys aware
there's like a pretty huge
civil war going on all across America?
Oh, sure, but we just try to stay out.
Stay out?
with what we see on the
news. Seems like it's for the best.
Yeah,
well, let me know if you
want to try anything on
Lee.
What?
You're so war torn
you can't try on a dress?
Jesus, you haven't seen yourself
in a mirror?
Oh my God, you didn't.
Shut the fuck up.
Turn around. I want to take your photo.
No. Come on.
Yes,
you're gonna take the photo.
Tell me not to rush.
Yeah, but there's a sweet
spot and you're missing it.
Don't wanna
miss your sweet spot.
Well, no,
that was not the moment.
Okay, one more.
Yes.
You're pretty when you smile.
- There you go.
- Hey,
- how about this?
- Yeah nice.
Not gonna take a picture,
right? You know
what, though?
Running a little long on film.
You mean.
I'm out.
I'm gonna try this on.
You actually bought something?
She did. It's paid now.
It's so weird. This place is
like everything I've forgotten.
Funny, I was thinking it
felt like everything I remembered.
Look at the tops of the buildings.
Be subtle.
Wouldn't have suited us anyway, Lee.
We'd have gotten bored.
I remain ready to accept the full,
immediate and unconditional surrender
of the secessionist
angels to liberate
the people of the subjugated
states and start rebuilding
our greek nation.
Words might as well be random.
What do you think he'll actually
say if I do get a mic in front of me?
Not much the ones that get taken.
Gaddafi, Mussolini, Ceausescu.
There are always lesser men than you think.
At the end.
He'll let you down, Joe.
As long as he isn't
dead before I get there.
Hold up.
It was a turn off three or 4 miles back.
Maybe we should turn
around and take another route.
Can you see anything?
Nothing. No shapes, no movement, nothing?
No.
Okay, I'm gonna drive forward a little.
Should we keep going?
Shit!
Where you going?
Them.
Don't be such a hot shot.
Just keep your head down.
No, shit.
Let me try driving on.
This guy's a good shot.
Hey, what's going on?
Someone in that house.
They're stuck.
We're stuck.
Who do you think they are?
No idea.
Hey. We're press.
Cool.
Now I understand why it's
written on the side of your vehicle.
Are you WF?
Who's giving you orders?
No one's giving us orders, man.
Someone's trying to kill us.
We are trying to kill them.
You don't know what side
they are fighting for.
Oh, I get it.
You're retarded.
You don't understand a word
I say.
Yo, what's over there in that house?
Someone shooting.
Guys, shut the fuck up.
I got good news.
Why don't you put your head down there?
I think so... I'm good.
Take it from an overhand
sleep any chance you get.
You never know what's
coming around the next corner.
- Sammy.
- What?
Got a car coming up on us
pretty fast.
What do you think?
- I don't know.
Maybe they're just in a hurry.
Oh, they're in a hurry, all right.
He smoked his tires
on the last one.
Okay,
well, we're not gonna
outrun anyone in this thing,
So, slow down a little, Lee. Let him pass.
Roger that.
Don't look out at them.
They just rolled on by.
What the fuck?
Tony.
- What the fuck?
- How you guys doing?
You just scared the shit out of me.
Good.
That was the idea.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I don't know, dude.
What are you doing here?
Fuck you.
God.
Small world.
Small world, my ass.
They were following us.
Did you tell them where we
were headed back in New York?
Fuck no.
Hey, Tony, did Joe tell you where
we were going back in New York?
I don't know, Lee.
He was pretty drunk when he was hitting
on that girl you got in the back seat.
You're a dick.
What can must have been so wasted.
Lee, I'm done with Bohai.
He loves the company.
He drives like a maniac.
Shoot your mom,
- Dude, what are you doing?
- I tell you.
Are you fucking crazy. Tony,
Don't worry.
I gotta do it.
- What?
I'm doing it.
Jesus, Lee, don't turn the wheel.
My new passenger.
Much better. Much better.
Bye-bye.
See you in Washington.
I told you, he drives like a maniac.
Where did they go?
This feels funny.
Where'd your guy go, Tony?
He's just fucking around, that's all.
I don't want him fucking around.
I want Jesse back in this car.
Relax, please. Look how fast
you can drive. The girl's fine.
How the fuck do you know
if she fine. Can you see them?
Oh.
We need to go down there now.
If we go down there,
they're going to kill us.
No, those aren't government forces.
Not up here.
Could have trespasses.
We're cool.
Those people do not want to
be seen doing what they're doing.
Tell us, Lee.
they're talking.
They're just giving them a scare.
They killed all the people
in that fucking truck.
They could have killed the
whole town.
But they'll stop now.
Who knows where those bodies are from?
Other bodies in uniform?
No, they're not.
- I'm going down.
- I'm coming with you.
Me too.
I'm telling you, every instinct and he
says, this is death. Okay? Death.
You stay.
Cause you're old, you can't run.
Fuck it. Shit.
Fuck this.
Why?
There's one hung up in there.
Hey. Hey, guys.
What's happening?
I guess there's some kind
of misunderstanding here.
Yeah?
- Yes, sir.
Those two guys over there,
they're my colleagues.
- What kind of colleagues?
- Journalist, Sir.
Were you actually just...
we were passing through.
- Passing through where? - Charlottesville.
Charlottesville?
- What's in Charlottesville? - Good hiking.
Are you?
Actually, we are.
No, we are covering the university campus
there.
They started a new program,
they are reopening the school,
which is a surreal feel good stuff.
I guess we all need that, right?
Yeah.
This guy's your calling?
- This guy here?
- Yes. Excuse me.
That guy.
Sir,
- Just...
- Just what?
Just what?
- You know what.
- What?
- Just please.
Just please,
Sir. Please.
- Yes, just speak.
We're american journalists.
You told me that already.
Okay, We-We work for Reuters.
Reuters doesn't sound american.
It's a news agency.
I know what Reuters is,
Sir.
Okay, I'm just saying.
- Just saying just what?
- We're american.
Okay?
Okay. What kind of american are you?
Central American.
South american?
What?
- Florida?
- Florida.
Central.
What about you?
Where are you from?
Tell him, Jesse.
- Missouri.
- It's Missouri state, right?
- Yes.
- You know what they call it?
Why they call it Missouri state?
- I don't know.
- You don't know?
It's american.
It is american. 100%.
What about you?
Where are you from?
- Colorado.
Colorado.
Missouri.
That's what I'm talking about.
America.
Who's this guy hiding over here?
Hey, buddy.
What's your deal?
Where are you from?
Huh? Where are you from?
Can't speak.
Are you mute?
You can't speak English?
Yes, you can.
Yes, you can. Okay.
Open your mouth and
tell me where you're from.
Just make sure it's clear
fucking English. Okay.
- Where are you from?
- I'm from Hong Kong.
Oh. China.
China.
Just stop it, okay?
Who the fuck.
Stop it.
Get in the car.
Get in the fucking car.
Gotta stop.
- What are you talking about?
- I can't drive.
We can't stop.
We gotta fucking drive.
I can't.
He's been hit.
He's bleeding.
No, no, no, no. Fuck.
Okay, get up. Get up.
We just heard about Sammy.
And there are two guys.
Tony, Bohai.
Their names.
Lee. I'm really sorry.
I know what he was to you.
- They're so fucked up.
- Oh, it's so fucked up.
It's so fucked up.
Now you wait until you hear
what these two have to say.
Joe, I'm just trying to talk,
to leave out Sammy.
I know. Yeah, I heard. Your
condolences means a lot.
Now just, just tell her
We loved Sammy.
Everyone did.
Thank you, Anya.
- Fuck.
The western forces are moving into DC.
Earlier today, the government
military basically surrendered.
Yeah, it's true.
DC's only protection now.
A few do or
die soldiers.
Handful of Secret Service.
WF's gonna roll right in.
So you and I, we're too late.
We missed the story.
And Sammy didn't even die
for anything good.
Bristol?
Processing.
Me too.
Hardly knew Sammy compared to you.
But yeah...
You knew the man you were with.
That's who he was.
It may sound fucked up,
But there are so many ways that it could
have ended for him.
And a lot of them were worse.
He didn't want to quit.
These last few days,
I've never been scared like that before.
And I've never felt more alive.
Get over here, now.
Oh my god.
So fucking close.
Western forces have reached
the White House perimeter.
The president is now surrounded.
We have...
Just give me a minute.
We're gonna have to go again.
You give him good
shit, leave on their. Boyle,
you
wf propelling out of a chopper
under the roof of the fucking Pentagon.
There's really only one shot though, huh?
You know who's in there?
They got intel from the generals
that surrendered yesterday.
The president's right
in that fucking building.
What do you hear they're
gonna do with him?
Kill?
No, capture.
Whoever gets a fucking gun.
Always had first.
Hey, Lee. Don't beat me to
the money side, huh?
Got the beast, two suburbans,
right outside.
President's on the move.
Fuck yeah.
He's busting out.
by western forces as
if attempted to escape.
He's not in there.
What?
Okay, let's go, let's go.
- What do you mean?
- Jesse, come on, now.
Pull me the moving out it.
This place is empty.
Stay the fuck out of our way.
I believe you're fire.
I'm alone.
Standing in the middle of
the touch briefing room.
I'm here to talk.
Flooded.
I'm here to negotiate the
surrender of the president.
He's here.
You the WF?
Take a wild guess.
Can the president be
entrusted into your safe care?
Yes, ma'am. We'll take
real good care of him.
Just bring him out here.
We're not bringing him anywhere
until we have agreed terms.
We need a guarantee of
safe passage for the president.
And we need extraction
to a neutral territory.
We request Greenland
or Alaska.
Nah, no terms.
Bring them out here.
We gotta move. Sergeant.
Ma'am, the president is willing...
Gunner, point.
Zack. Moving.
Just go...
get back.
I'm out. Reloading. Reloading.
Crash it.
Chief, clip left.
The cross check.
Forward gunner,
I'm moving across. I
need your legs to fire.
Sergeant, you're going left.
Copy. Yo, ready?
Move. Move.
Good. Stay down.
Deacon, flag. Move. Stay.
Move up. Move.
Get him up. Moving.
Ready. Break up.
Break up. Break up.
Reload it.
Perfect trash.
Wait,
wait.
I need a quote.
Don't, don't kill me.
Yeah.
Don't do.