Subtitle : ByME
We are now closer
than we have ever been.
We are now closer than we have ever been.
To victory.
Some... Some are already
calling it the greatest.
Some are already calling it
the greatest victory in
the history of mankind.
Some are calling it already.
We are closer than we
have ever been to victory.
Some are already
calling it the greatest
victory in the history
of military campaigns.
Today I can announce that the so called
western forces of Texas and California
have suffered a very great
loss, a very great defeat
at the hands of the fighting men and women
of the United States military.
The people of Texas and California
should know that they will be welcomed
back to these United States
as soon as their illegal
secessionist government is deposed.
I can also confirm that the Florida
alliance has failed in its attempt to
force the brave people of the
Carolinas into joining the insurrection.
Citizens of America, we are now
closer than ever to a historic victory
as we eliminate the final
pockets of resistance.
God bless you all and God bless America.
you okay?