[music]
(humming)
Ho ho ho, That logo music just
gets you pumped, right?
I'm sorry, I'm just excited to be here.
It's been a while.
You know for a long time, I
wasn't sure I'd ever be back.
Disney bought Fox, there was a whole
boring rights issue,
blahpadee blahpadee blah.
But then, it turned out they wanted me?
The one guy who shouldn't
even have his own movie.
Much less a franchise.
Heh heh Marvel's so stupid.
Look, we know the title of this thing, so
I know what you're wondering.
How are we going to do this without
dishonoring Logan's memory?
And I'll tell you how.
We're not.
Only you
I'm going to let you
in on a little secret.
Wolverine is not dead.
Sure, it made for a perfect
ending to a very sad story,
but that's not how
regenerative healing factors work.
You think I want to be out here in
beautiful downtown North Dakota,
digging up the one and only Wolverine?
No, thank you.
But the fate of my
entire world is at stake.
He may not be living his best life, but
he sure as hell ain't dead.
Bingo.
Yahtzee.
Ah yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
Damn it!
Son of a bitch!
Fuck! Motherfucker!
My world is fucked!
That was weird.
I'm much calmer now.
Look, I'm not a man of science,
but you seem incredibly passed away.
But it's good to see ya.
I gotta be honest, I've always wanted to
ride with you, Log.
You and me getting into it
Deadpool and a Wolverine.
Just fucking shit up.
Can you imagine the fun,
the chaos, the residuals?
Good day mate.
There's nothing that'll bring me back to
life faster than a
big bag of Marvel cash.
Me too, Hugh.
But no, no, no, no.
Ugh, he had to get all
noble and die for real.
God damn it!
I could really use your help right now.
Wait!
I'm warning you! I'm not alone!
Wade Winston Wilson!
You are under arrest by
the Time Variance Authority!
With too many crimes for this, come out!
God.. Oh...
death by day player.
Last chance!
Throw out your weapons
and come out peacefully!
I'm not gonna give you my weapons!
But I promise not to use them.
There are 206 bones in the human body.
207 if I'm watching Gossip Girl.
Here we go, maximum effort.
Okay Peanut, guess we're getting
that team up after all.
I'm doing this tonight
You're probably gonna start a fight
I know this can't be right
Hey baby come on
I loved you endlessly
When you weren't there for me
So now it's time to leave
And make it alone
I know that I can't take no more
It ain't no lie
I want to see you out that door
Baby bye bye bye
Don't want to be a fool for you
Just another player
in your game for two
You may hate me
but it ain't no lie
Baby bye bye bye
Bye bye
Don't really want to make it tough
I just want to tell you that I've had enough
It might sound crazy
But it ain't no lie
Baby bye bye bye
You just hit me
with the truth, now
girl you're more than welcome to
Maradona, from outside the box!
GOAAALLLLLLLLLL!
Now baby come on
I know that I can't take no more
It ain't no lie
I want to see you out that door
Baby bye bye bye
Bye bye
Don't want to be a fool for you
Just another player
in your game for two
You may hate me
but it ain't no lie
Baby bye bye bye
Don't really want to make it tough
I just want to tell you
that I've had enough
Might sound crazy but it ain't no lie
Baby
bye bye bye
I don't wanna be your fool
In this game for two
So I'm leaving
you behind
I don't want to make it tough
But I've had enough
Oh baby
Don't want to be  a fool for you
Just another player
in your game for two
I don't want to be your fool
But it ain't no lie
Baby bye
bye bye
Don't really want to make it tough
I just want to tell you that I've had enough
It might sound crazy
But it ain't no lie
Bye bye bye bye
(Metal claws coming out)
I am soaking wet right now.
(screaming) To be clear, I'm not
proud of any of this.
The waft of violence,
the whiff of necrophilia,
it isn't who I am, it
isn't who I wanna be.
Who I wanna be?
Well, to help you understand that,
I gotta take you back.
My little joy ride I
took through space and time,
to the day that changed everything.
(dramatic music)
(gunshots)
I can't believe I'm finally here.
I've waited for this moment for so long.
Thank you, sir, for seeing me.
I firmly believe that my
services could be of great use
to your organization.
Now, I know I was caught smashsturbating
in the lobby of Stark Tower.
Smashturbating?
But I can assure you that.
I'm sorry, what was that?
No, I'm sorry.
That's when you get
those toy Hulk hands, right?
And then you just, you
look down and you just,
you brace yourself and
you ravage the midsection.
I get it, okay, thank you.
The picture's painted.
You get the gist.
What exactly brings you here today?
Well I, wow okay, I care.
I know I turn
everything into a joke,
but I care and I want to use that feeling
for something important.
I want to matter.
And to show my girl that I matter.
And, you know, I feel like I'm wasting
the good stuff here.
Is the man not going to be joining us?
The man?
Yeah, I should say this if he's going to.
As far as you can tell
right now, I'm the man.
The man is me.
I am the man in this circumstance.
And he doesn't do this
kind of thing anymore.
Cameos?
Meetings.
Entry-level meetings.
Entry-level?
Aren't you the chauffeur?
I, maybe.
Common misconception,
I did begin my career
as Mr. Stark's driver.
I quickly pivoted to
the head of security.
The head of security?
The head of security, of
course, yes, yes, yes, yes.
And why I am vetting your resume.
You seem to have left out whether or not
you had any experience
as a member of a team.
Could you maybe add a
little bit of perspective?
Oh, yes, of course.
I was Special Forces, but I was mainly,
I was team leader,
founder, really, of X-Force.
Sadly, they all perished in action.
How exactly did that happen?
Well, the police say
gravity, but just between us,
they didn't test well in the focus group.
Particularly Cable.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, I
can see this isn't going on.
Please stop writing.
I'm just, I want to be an Avenger.
I want to be an Avenger.
Why do you want to be an Avenger?
Well look around you, I mean,
they're the best of the best.
And what they do matters.
I need to be an Avenger.
Sir, my girl has kinda had
it with my shtick,
and if I don't, you
know, turn things around
and do something with my gifts,
I don't think it's going
to really work out for me,
and I wouldn't blame her.
Avengers are a very
unique group of superheroes
that stand for something
more than just fighting
and wearing costumes.
I mean, people look up
to us. Kids look up to us.
I'm sorry, us?
I wasn't aware that you were an Avenger.
Avengers adjacent, technically.
Oh, what's your
superpower? Is it parallel parking?
I am so sorry. That was cruel.
I lash out when I'm
nervous. It won't happen again.
Let's cut to the chase. Please.
You just said moments ago
that you wanted to be an Avenger
because you need it.
Yes, sir, I do.
But the Avengers don't do
the job because they need it.
They do the job because people need them.
Do you see the distinction?
Yes, sir.
Please, Mr. Hogan, I don't
want to spend the rest of my life
like an annoying one-trick pony.
All right.
Oh, my God. You're standing.
Yeah, now's the time that we stand.
Damn it.
The problem might be that
you're reaching a little too high.
Aim for the middle and you'll never miss.
Right? I think you got a good heart. I
believe what you're saying.
But not everybody's a world-saving type.
I'm not. I'm happy. Right?
I found my place.
Find your place.
All right. Get back out there.
We'll keep an eye on you. Good luck.
Mm-mm. Mm-mm. Mm-mm.
Fetch the car. I want to hit Shake Shack.
Rejection makes me hungy.
No, no, no. Please.
No, no, no. Okay.
You know what they say?
When one door closes,
your locker at work opens.
Let's go sell some certified
pre-owned vehicles, motherf--
Technically, the
Carnival's not a minivan.
It's an MPV.
So how does the Kia
compare to the Honda Odyssey?
The Odyssey? That's a great question.
It doesn't fucking suck.
You know, you can answer
the question without swearing.
I'm sorry. Tammy I don't have kids.
Not that I haven't dreamt of that.
I don't have a lot of vaginal sex.
You'll get them next time, pal. Yeah.
And look, you can always
go back to super-heroing.
I mean, I know I'd like to
be back in the suit.
I don't keep it in my
locker so that I can wear it.
I keep it in my locker in
case we need to saddle up again.
Hey, hey, hey. What
is that doing in there?
I'm done.
Ane I'm fine with being done.
Look, is sales the best match?
Probably none.
Is this the life that I
always imagined for myself?
Fuck no!
This is the right fit for me.
Sugar Bear, it is. Okay, Mr. Wilson.
I'm just saying, once a month, we could
go on a little mission.
We're human beings. We crave purpose.
After all, we're Deadpool.
Please stop saying
that. We're not Deadpool.
I'm not even Deadpool anymore.
Well, if you're gonna have
a midlife crisis, go big.
A few years ago, a friend of
mine got his nipples pierced
with a titanium chain that goes down and
attaches to his Van Johnson.
Are you feeling Grumple
Stiltskin because it's your birthday?
What?
No.
Surprise!
All right, you guys
are lucky I'm not armed.
Get in here.
This was six years
ago. You'd all be dead.
So then, he gets out of the cab, and you
would not believe it.
I turn around, and what do I find?
Airpods. His Airpods!
Crazy stories. Every time.
Come on. Every single time.
Make any sales today?
You know I didn't.
Did you sell any
dreamcatchers on Etsy or whatever it is that you do?
Our rent's due in three days Wade, and I
can't keep carrying it. Relax.
I have the money. I sold some old blood
pressure medication I found lying around.
You're trying to kill me, motherfucker.
I'm not the one dousing
everything in salt, motherfucker.
I pray every day that fire finds your
body and finishes the job
God didn't have the nuts to do.
That's hurtful. If you could hear the
look on my face,
you'd smell how sad I am.
You watching anything good?
Great British Bake-off.
Oh, God damn.
This shit stood between me
and suicide for ten years.
Those are my feelings.
Abortion, religious freedom, animal
rights, privacy rights, vaccines, free
market capitalism, global climate change.
No, no, no, no speaking lines Buck.
Hi, Yukio. Hi, Wade.
Nice, fake o'clock shadow.
It's a summer balayage from the French.
It's meant to mimic the natural
highlights of the sun.
It's a toupee. It's a hair system.
I love your hair system, Wade.
Thank you.
Want to do some cocaine? Hey, cocaine is
the one thing that
Feige said is off-limits.
What about Bolivian marching powder? They know
all the slang terms. They have a list.
Even snowboarding? Even disco dust.
White girl interrupted? Even Forrest Bump.
Focus shit. I wouldn't
even try powdered gonuts.
Do you want to build a
snowman? Yes, but I can't.
Pull here. Here?
What happened? That's the fun part.
Thanks for coming. Yeah.
How's work? Oh, I got a promotion.
No way. Yeah.
It's mind-numbing middle
management, but I'm happy.
That's great.
You seeing anyone? How are you?
Um, yeah. A guy from work.
Dermot. Dermot?
He's kind. Good.
Likes to go hiking.
Hasn't gotten me shot yet.
Wow. It's the early days.
How about you? You seeing anyone?
No, no, I live in a one-bedroom
apartment. Share a bed with blind Al.
All right. All right.
Happy birthday to you.
Okay, okay, okay.
Birthdays.
Every spin around the moon
is a new adventure indeed.
Sun dumbass! Okay, round-earther.
Where was I? The Adventure of Life.
Right. It's been a challenging few years.
I haven't seen you guys in a while.
Been through a lot. Change of life.
Menopause? Bitch, are you improv-ing?
I'm sorry that you had
to see that, Yukio.
But I'm happy.
You know, that's because of
each and every one of you.
I guess what I'm trying to say is how
proud I am, how grateful I am,
to be standing in a room with every
single person I love.
I'm the luckiest man alive.
Make a wish, buddy. 10-4, good buddy.
Going down.
Wade Wilson? Oh, yeah. Dancers.
Dopinder must have ordered you. Are
those supposed to be cop costumes?
Never mind. Take your
clothes off, but leave the helmets.
And this isn't Pretty
Woman. We're kissing, all right?
What song do you guys normally dance to?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Is that supposed to be scary?
Pegging isn't new for me,
friendo, but it is for Disney.
Look, I've never been a natural bottom.
So we're going to take things real slow,
and I want some crazy eye contact.
Not you, you.
I can't see your eyes through
the mask, but I can feel it.
We're going to move on down the hallway
so we can spare a cleanup on aisle asshole.
How does everyone feel about this plan?
I don't like you. Yes.
Let's hold on to that attitude,
and we're going to do it angry.
[ominous music]
Mr. Wilson.
You appear to have soiled
yourself while unconscious.
I wasn't unconscious. Who are you?
I go by the name of Paradox, Mr. Paradox,
and you're sitting here at the TVA, the
Time Variance Authority.
We're really a watchdog organization.
Except we're more
lighthearted than that sounds,
with sort of throwback ironic twist.
And we're in charge of defending what's
known as the sacred timeline.
Holy fuck, that is a shit ton of
exposition for a three-quel.
Is this because I used Cable's Time
Machine, brought a
couple of people back to life,
then I destroyed it.
That was a long time ago.
Yes, we're aware of your
abuse of your timeline.
You were so abusive of it.
No, it has nothing to do
with that. Walk with me.
I brought you here, Mr. Wilson, to tell
you that you're special.
In fact, you've been
chosen for a higher purpose,
a purpose unclear even to me,
but one that could save
the entire sacred timeline
from a possibly grizzly
fate sometime in the future,
which may very well need to be avenged.
This sacred timeline, I assume I'm going
to marvel at how cinematic it feels,
gratuitous cameos, indiscriminate use of
variants, the whole package.
No, you tell me.
Cap.
You are no longer lost.
Wade.
You can be a hero among the heroes.
We've been surveilling
you for quite a while.
Subway station.
The TVA outpost, yes.
And what is that?
Is that me? Is that Thor?
Is he crying?
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
That happens in the distant future.
Why is Thor crying?
Quick tell me. Do not speak to her.
Stop that. Eyes on me, I brought you
here to offer you an opportunity,
the opportunity you sought years ago but
for which you were not ready.
We believe you're ready now,
ready for a chance to leave your timeline
and join the greatest universe of all.
I am about to give you the
thing you've always wanted.
Oh I smell what you're stepping in.
The power of the Marvel
universe is about to change forever.
I am the Messiah.
I am...
Marvel Jesus.
Can you excuse me for just one-
I'm just gonna go over here
Suck it, Fox.
I'm going to Disneyland.
Get fucked!
Where do I sign?
Oh, there's no need for paper work.
Good. Not to brag, but I do not read.
There is one thing I will need, though.
Oh, fuck off.
Adorn me, Beardo.
Fuckin' A!
It's perfect.
FYI, your tailor is a
predator, but I love it.
Snug, no camel toe, new
car smell, and adamantium.
Katanas, you shouldn't have.
Go ahead. Take it in.
And yes, your
underwear is getting tighter.
That guy knows what I'm talking about.
His clothes say middle management, but
his eyes say fucky fucky.
Yes, you look very nice.
Nice? Your buddy here is ready to throw
it all away from me.
You calling your wife?
HR.
Is your wife working HR?
I'm really glad
you're taking this so well.
Oh, I'm taking it well.
I have never had a
problem traveling for work.
That said, we should talk vacation days.
I'm more of a one-week-on,
one-week-off kind of guy.
I think it's what they do in Denmark.
You'll never see a Danish
flag on the moon, but...
God damn it, they're happy.
Now, let's power up your
little Amazon Fire Phone there
and zip me back home so
I can let my friends know
that they've been upgraded, to Disciples.
Yep. I don't think that you quite understand.
You will not be returning to your home
because there will be
no home to return to.
Come again, this time in my ears?
This is your universe, Mr. Wilson.
That, is what happens when a universe
loses their anchor being.
See how it decays from the inside?
This is how a reality dies.
What's an anchor being?
An anchor being is an
entity of such vital importance
that when they die, their whole world
slowly withers out of existence.
You've just won the
lottery because I didn't die.
It's just a little
midlife crisis, I'm better now.
Oh, my God!
Oh, not to laugh.
Can you imagine if you
were the anchor being?
Yeah.
No, it isn't you, Mr. Wilson.
Your anchor being died in
an act of self-sacrifice
so epic that it sent
shivers down the timeline.
I am referring, of
course, to Logan, the Wolverine.
Don't be like me.
(Music)
Oh, this is what it feels like.
Logan.
Of course.
Logan!
The guy with forks for hands!
That Wolverine!
Yeah, I got it.
You can turn your retro
graphics of death off now.
Make it stop.
We're not doing it, Mr. Wilson. We
certainly can't stop it.
How long have we got?
In most cases, a couple thousand years.
Well, sweet.
Most cases aren't
fast enough, not for me.
What does that mean?
It means that I have been tasked with
overseeing the end of your universe
and regardless of what the pencil pushers
upstairs would prefer,
I will not waste my life watching it die
slowly of natural causes.
We used to just prune these things,
simple, elegant, efficient,
but I'm told the TVA
doesn't like to do that anymore.
Well, I do.
And no matter what my
so-called superiors say,
the multiverse does
not need a babysitter.
We need a mercy killer.
And in this instance,
I am the mercy killer.
What in the macguffin is that?
That's a time-ripper for Mr. Wilson.
An accelerant.
Once completed, it will allow me to
destroy the space-time
matrix of your universe.
You see, I don't want
to work for the TVA.
I want to be the TVA.
And the first step involves showing this
organization how much more
efficient it can become to it.
I will be giving your universe a swift
and compassionate end.
And don't worry, your
friends won't feel a thing.
It'll be over just like this.
Oh, what's that? Ugh!
Trust me.
You're gonna Old Yeller
my fucking universe?
In your parlance, yes.
Two in the heart, one in the head.
Look, Mr. Wilson, you have two choices.
You can either rejoin your loved ones and
collectively cease to
exist in, I'd say, 72 hours,
or you join the sacred timeline.
And you end your days of
insignificance and mediocrity.
Wade.
Wade, you can finally, finally matter.
That's all I've ever really wanted.
I know.
And you know, I'm nothing
if not morally flexible.
Hmm?
Yep, yep.
I'll do it.
Wise choice.
Sacred timeline's happy to have you.
I was talking about finding the Wolverine
and breaking your fucking nose.
(Iris by Goo Goo Dolls plays)
Find him.
Find him!
And boy, did he ever.
Which brings us back to this.
The desecration of the sacred corpse.
Ow, my own fucking arm.
[screaming]
Now we're talking! Agh my nads!
Oh dear god!
I'm sorry, Wolverining is hard!
Make it stop!
Mangle tried.
[screaming]
You sick fuck.
Logan was a hero and the only thing
worth a shit to
ever come out of Canada.
[screaming]
Get my country's name
out of your fucking mouth.
And my sword.
Gimme that.
Oh, I gotta find me another Logan.
An alive one.
Don't get up, guys. I'll see myself out.
Logan!
I'm gonna need you to come with me.
Who's asking?
Well, look at this
little hairy Lou Retton.
Did you stick the landing little guy?
Yes, you did, comic-accurate short king.
Such a cute widdle, wolvie.
Cue the fucking montage, baby.
Ahoy, everything
seems to be on fire.
Do you have a dragon?
Ooh, you have anchor
being written all over.
Patch.
Now we're talking.
Ooh, yeah.
That's a whole
goddamn package right there.
Howdie, I'm auditioning anchor beings.
Oh, now that's gonna need some coconut oil.
What in the fuck?
Are you okay?
Oh, yes, yes.
Classic John Byrne brown in 10.
Now you fought the Hulk in
this outfit, no?
I'm Marvel Jesus, you dull
creature, and I want to--
It's not you. We're just going
in a different direction.
You know, from behind, you
look a little bit like Henry--
Oh, my fuck.
The Cavillrine. The legends are true.
And may I say, sir, on
behalf of all humanity,
this just feels right.
We will treat you so much better than
those shit-fucks down the street
You were just leaving.
No, sir, not while the
fate of my universe is at--
This one looks promising.
Down you go.
Again.
I told you, you're not welcome here.
You're not welcome anywhere.
Now get the fuck out of my bar.
Just give me one more
drink and then I'll leave.
That's not how it works.
It does now. Leave the bottle.
I know you, bub?
Nope. But I know you.
Everybody knows me.
I'm the Wolverine.
Yes, you are, and I'm gonna need you to
come with me right now.
Look, lady, I'm not interested.
Really getting into your cups here--
Why would I go with you?
Because, unfortunately, I need you.
And even more unfortunately
my entire world needs you.
You two gonna fuck or fight?
You gonna take that from him?
Yup.
I can tell you have a sort
of don't get too close,
I'll only break your heart vibe going here.
But every other Wolverine would have
really hurt me by now.
And I'm sort of on the tic-tic, so,
upsy-daisy, here we go.
Hey hey.
Whoa.
Whiskey dick with the claws.
It's quite common in Wolverines over 40.
You don't want this.
You're right, I don't.
And you don't want this.
Unless you want to take a deep breath
through your fucking forehead,
I suggest you reconsider.
Let's go, Peanut.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Hold on.
Watch this.
All right.
That's whoa.  Easy.
Good God.
Thirsty little honey badger, aren't you?
It's okay. Keep going.
Audiences are
accustomed to long run times.
I guess you'll have to do...
Okay.
Ooh.
Look at those jammies.
That only took 20 fucking years.
One anchor being coming right up.
On your left, baby girl.
This Logan has the same... he can do
anything even musicals.
But, notice, he's
actually wearing a costume
like he's not embarrassed to be in a
superhero movie for once.
I don't understand.
You said my universe is dying,
because this sack of
nuts got himself killed.
Well, problem solved.
My God.
You actually think you can replace an
anchor being, with this!?
I wouldn't have accepted any other
Wolverine b-t-dubs,
but you have outdone yourself and brought
me the worst Wolverine!
What do you mean the worst one?
Mr. Wilson, this Wolverine
let down his entire world.
He's the stuff of
legend, but not in a good way.
And what he did... well, some things are
just beyond forgiveness.
Okay. How do I make this right?
I'll do anything.
I gave you a chance at greatness,
because my superiors
deemed you special.
Clearly not special in a good way,
but apparently you have some important
future purpose to serve.
With Thor, he holds me.
But I did my duty.
I gave you the
opportunity to be somebody,
and instead of accepting my offering with
humility and gratitude,
you broke my nose.
Ah, It looks great.
and you decimated dozens of my men with the
exhumed corpse of a hero,
dishonoring not only
his remains, but his memory.
What are you, the internet?
Your world is dying!
Thank you very much.
And there's no stopping it.
The humane thing to do is to make it quick.
Is the thought of vaporizing
my universe making you peckish?
I'm eating my feelings.
I'm about to lose everything
that I've ever cared about,
because that hairy thundercunt from down
undercunt finally dies,
and he's standing
right behind me, isn't he?
Welcome to the MCU, by the way.
You're joining at a bit of a low point.
As for you, I want to talk to your boss.
I want you to get him on the phone,
and you tell him, her, or them
that Marvel H. Christ isn't playing.
Holy shit.
I just heard a symphony of buttholes
clenching all at once.
You're off-grid.
Your bosses don't know what you sick
fucks are doing down here.
Well, I'll tell you what.
I have a black belt in Karen, and I'm
gonna go upstairs,
and I'm going to tell
them all about you and--
Oh, silence is nice. Isn't it.
Where the fuck did he go?
To the trash heap.
You'll fit right in.
That was close.  Ha ha!
Don't just stand there, you ape.
Give me a hand up.
Nope, I'm actually okay. Thank you.
Where the hell are we?
I don't know.
Looks kind of Mad Maxie.
But that would be IP infringement, right?
Fucking jokes.
Were you even listening back there?
We don't make it back to
that Mr. Paradox asshole.
Everyone I know is going to die.
Not my fucking problem.
Well, is that all you got?
Is that what you said
when your world went to shit?
Come again?
Yeah, I heard all about you.
How you screwed up everything,
and you should be thanking me for pulling
you out of that bed you shit in.
Agh you backstabbing son of a bitch?
Are you ready to be calm now?
Rest in peace, you fucks.
I don't want to fight you, Peanut.
Doesn't matter what you did.
I just need your help.
I don't fucking care.
Fuck! This is gonna hurt.
Alright!
Fuck it!
Let's give the people what they came for.
Let's fucking go.
Get your special sock out, nerds.
This gonna get good.
Baby knife
Let's see you grow
your fucking head back!
Wait wait wait, I can fix it! I can fix it!
Fix what? Whatever it is that you did.
Whatever made you so bad.
Those... those...
pricks In the TVA, you heard them.
They have the power to end my universe.
But they also have the
power to change yours.
We get back there.
And we can fix your world.
Together.
I promise.
They can fix it.
Hey!
We fight each other, we lose.
Dear God, it's him.
Who? The one.
The superhero equivalent
to comfort food or Molly.
White guy's answer to all the
disappointments at another A-lister.
Fair warning, gorgeous.
You're going to
encounter some delicate language.
A smidge of ass play, but we've been
prohibited from using cocaine, on camera.
They're coming.
Who's they?
[engine revving]
Oh, they're driving angry.
Now that's a superhero landing!
I got this.
[engine revving]
Stay close.
Aye aye Captain.
You got this.
Cassandra is going to be giddy when she
sees what we caught.
You can't run. Everybody knows that.
You see anyone running, dick for brains?
You're not going to love
what happens next.
Oh, oh my God.
Oh my God, oh my God he's gonna to say it. Ah fuck!
Ha! Oh my God, he's going to say it!
Say what?
Avengers, assemb-
Flame on! Sorry, what now?
[Fire whooshing]
[screaming]
Oh, fuck!
[crash]
We don't know that guy.
We thought we did.
I know you.
Holy sh--
[growling]
Sabretooth, your brother.  Ready to die!?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait! Time!
You look ridiculous.
People have waited
decades for this fight.
It's not going to be easy.
Baby knife.
Shoot the double, take him down.
Side control, then full mount,
and you ground and pound till he makes
no sound because he's dead.
Shut the fuck up.
Oh my God.
Okay, good luck. I'm a huge fan.
[foreboding tune]
[laughing]
[growling]
What is it, girl?
Is there trouble at the well?
[head drops]
[laughing]
Big trouble.
Behold!
The head of your precious queen, Furiosa!
I have the Wolverine.
I alone control her.
You come for me!
You come for her.
So sorry. I know it's pronounced him.
I'm genderblind. It's my cross to bear.
Who's next?
Toad!
You're up.
[metal clanging]
[grunting]
Uh-oh.
Holy shi-
[crash]
Uh.
I should've...
God of Thunder.
(grunting)
How long was I asleep?
Not all of you was asleep.
Don't bother.
They're very thorough.
If you know where we are, start talking.
You're in the void.
Think of it as purgatory.
Reed called it a metaphysical junkyard
where anything useless goes
before it gets annihilated
forever and where the TVA sends people
that don't play nice
with the rest of the multiverse.
Like you?
And you.
What does the annihilating?
Alioth.
Alioth is in this thing?
From Loki season one episode five?
Everyone here is on the run from Alioth.
Oh, most don't make it.
There's a resistance though.
Other people like us
that managed to survive,
they're hiding out in the borderlands
trying to find a way the fuck outta here.
Then that's where we go.
We?
Us?
A team?
The answer is yes.
Shake on it.
Fuck!
You nipped it.
Just got the tip with
your little steak knife.
These others can help
us get back to the TVA.
They can fix things.
(laughing)
Something funny, bub?
She might have
something to say about that.
Who's she?
In the void.
You're either food for a
Alioth or you work for her.
(dramatic music)
(engine revving)
Heh, Paul Rudd finally aged.
Oh, you must be this year's Juggernaut.
Thank you.
I'd keep your voices down.
She don't like the chatter.
She's gonna love you.
(foreboding music)
Is that Charles?
Hey, hey, Chuck, it's us!
That's not the Chuck.
Ah, shit.
Oh, ableism, great.
That's not gonna go over
well with the woke mob.
A Wolverine.
I wondered when I'd get one of you.
You're one of Xavier's.
You know him, you know Chuck?
Oh, I knew him.
We shared a womb.
Tried to strangle the sly little fellow
with my umbilical cord.
Amen.
I've never loved roommates.
Mine's blind, except she could see
cocaine for some reason.
You wanna chime in, Your Majesty?
I'm dying here.
Who are you?
Charles Xavier's twin, Cassandra Nova.
Bullshit. How was the anal birth?
You two are cute.
I have a good feeling about this.
(chains falling)
And I've been trying to
catch this little firefly
for years, haven't I, Johnny?
Oh, you picked the wrong
time to make new friends.
Oh, Johnny told us all about you.
Maybe shut up now.
Yeah, maybe don't-- We
were just talking here.
Yeah, Johnny told us you're a psychotic,
megalomaniacal asshole.
His word's not mine.
Hell bent, on domination in pain.
You said all that about me.
No, no!
How do you, I just say anything!
Sticks and stones, Johnny!
Don't let her intimidate you.
It's like you said in the convoy.
This finger-licking, dead inside,
pixie slab of
third-rate dime store nut milk
can eat your delicious cinnamon ring
and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
I have never said any of those words
in my entire life!
Have some modesty!
People think I'm a shit-talker,
but this guy, next level.
What?
This, I, wait, I don't even know what
half of that means!
My hat's off to you, sir, truly.
I didn't, he's, that's, I, I, I don't--
(splattering)
Not my favorite, Chris.
You stupid piece of shit, you
just got him fucking killed!
Hey, we're all grieving!
PS, do you know what he was
doing to the budget?
(shushing)
Alioth is hungry.
There's been some kind of mistake.
Big Yellow is a backup anchor being,
and I'm Marvel Jesus, MJ if you're nasty.
This may be hard to hear,
but there's another British villain.
He's gonna destroy my
universe, and I'm gonna stop him.
Oh, honey, you don't really strike me
as a world-saving type.
Did I hit a nerve?
I didn't want it to come to this.
Either you help us, or my friend here
is gonna sing the entire
second act of Music Man,
with zero warmup.
Where'd you get the chair?
Well once in a while, I did
get a Charles through here.
Nevermind, though, no.
He didn't care to find me.
Agh, Gen-Z and your trauma-bragging!
Can't you just stuff it
down, turn it into accomplishment
or cancer like the rest of us?
But I'm not like the rest of you.
Except maybe the Wolverine.
Now we could be truly
terrifying together.
You're that scary, huh?
The TVA certainly thought so.
They sent me here before I could walk.
And you know, it's the best thing that
ever happened to me.
I love it here.
You live in a garbage dump.
I think we both know who
lives in the garbage dump.
The void is a paradise.
I can wield my power here without shame.
Unfortunately, I had no Charles Xavier
to teach me temperance.
What about your Charles?
Did he protect you?
Did he make you feel safe?
We're mutants, we're never safe.
(screaming)
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
I don't want the smoke.
I don't have any beef with you.
I just want to save my friends.
I just, I want to go home.
Well, the thing is, I could get you home.
Good.
But I don't want to.
Not good.
(grunting)
What do you want, Wade Wilson?
Uh, your fingers are inside
me, but not in a good way.
My brother could enter
one's mind with a thought.
I have to get my hands dirty.
Agh, God.
Shh shh shh shh I've got you.
I've got you.
Wade
I can't reach you when you're not here.
I'm right here.
No, you're not, I can't.
Then show me. You gotta do something.
Show you what?
Show me you care about
something bigger than you.
Ever since they turned
you down, you took a knee.
Baby, you never got back up.
I know you're going through something.
Let me go through it with you.
Your crazy matches my crazy.
Where'd you go?
Oh my God.
You just say it, okay?
Say, "I don't want you"
"I don't want to be with you."
Go ahead, say it, say it, say it, say it.
You don't want to be with me.
Tell me that and I'll walk away.
Say, "I don't want you."
(somber music)
You'll never fucking matter.
What?
She never said that.
No, but I bet she thought it.
Uhh blu-blugh, ugh!
You are so mean.
My brain could taste your fingers
and they tasted like hate.
And where in God's name is
the intimacy coordinator?
You're so lost, Mr. Wilson.
And long before you came here.
This is Baby Knife, she's
gonna fuck you in the face now.
If you want to kill me,
it's going to take
more than a little blade.
How about six?
(stabbing sound)
Ha ha haaa.
My boy's wicked strong.
That's my big boy, yes you are.
(laughs)
(wooshing noise)
Well, this has been fun,
but the big guy needs to
eat and the rent is due.
(menacing sounds)
By the way, you're the rent.
(menacing sounds) (screams)
(metal clanging)
Give a
Fuck!
You coming or what?
Coming!
(engine revs)
(engine sputtering)
(grunting sounds)
Whatcha thinking bout?
Get the fuck off of me.
Shh, shh.
Almost done.
Almost done what?
Getting my knife out of your buttocks.
Pervert! Ah, fuck!
Get your mind out of my pants.
I'm telling Blake.
New rules.
I talk now.
That's gonna be very
hard on the audience.
Shut the fuck up!
Let me fucking think.
Now we gotta get back to Paradox, right?
Right!?
Je m'excuse? (Exuse me?)
Am I allowed to speak now or--
Just nod, asshole.
Right.
Then we find the others.
That poor kid Johnny was talking about
before you got him killed.
Poor kid, he's like 50.
If there's a chance they
know how to get out of here,
we find him and make those TVA fuckers
fix my shit like you fucking promised.
I smell quest.
I smell food.
So what made you finally
wear an honest to God costume?
Mine's red so they can't see me bleed.
But I can see how
yellow would be useful too.
Have you been checked for ADHD?
Nn-nn.
But I've had several STDs,
which were probably caused by ADHD.
What are you looking for?
Oh, thank fuck.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's rubbing alcohol.
You don't wanna drink-oh.
Yup, there you go.
Fuck that liver.
Good. Okay.
What the fuck are those?
Oh.
Back in civilian life, I wear a toupee,
but nobody knows.
(laughs) Everybody knows.
Wanna talk about what's haunting you
or should we wait for
a third act flashback?
Ah go fuck yourself.
You know,
in my world, you're um. You're well regarded.
Yeah, well, not in mine.
They don't like me much in mine either.
You don't say.
I wanted to be something.
You know, I, shit.
I wanted to be an Avenger.
Fuck the Avengers.
Yeah, I didn't make the cut though.
Same with the X-Men.
When girlfriend left me
You had a girlfriend?
Yeah.
Vanessa, when we met, she was a dancer.
We had a whole life. It was good.
But oh boy, I just, mwah
fucked that right up.
But you, you were an X-Men.
Fuck that, you were the X-Man.
You.
The Wolverine.
He was a hero in my world.
Yeah, well, he ain't shit in mine.
You said Logan was a hero, what happened?
He died.
How?
Well, technically you
were chest fucked by a tree,
but really you just ran out of batteries
trying to save someone.
Who?
The shit heels that grew her
in a lab called her X-23.
But she was just a kid.
A younger, daintier,
somehow meaner version of you.
He died trying to save her.
It was beautiful.
Look, Mijo, I know you're hurtin.
My blind, elderly
African-American roommate,
Blind Al, always says that
pain teaches us who we are.
Sometimes we need to listen to that pain
instead of running from it.
Holy shit.
Yeah, she's wise.
No, no, no that's her
name, you call her Blind Al.
Well, she's blind.
(Lady in Red plays)
I've never seen you looking
as lovely as you did tonight
I've never seen you shine so bright
Lady in red
Is dancing with me
She did, she did
There's nobody here
Look at you.
She's coming with us.
No, she's not.
Oh, yes, she is.
Fuck, no.
Oh, yes. Sorry.
Sorry about that.
Come here, girl.
Who are you?
I'm Deadpool.
And I guess you're Deadpool too.
But in here, everybody calls me Nicepool.
Oh my goodness, wait till
do you see Ladypool.
She is gorgeous.
She just had a baby
too, and-  Can't even tell.
I don't think you're
supposed to say that.
That's okay.
I identify as a feminist, right?
Are those gold-plated, 50 caliber
desert eagle pistoleros?
Of course.
To match my ear huggy.
Can I have them?
(laughs) Over my dead body.
You're fun.
And I guess you've
already met Mary Puppins.
It's AKA Dogpool.
Careful where you put your
hand, she's 90% G-Spot,
and she'll let you know it.
You let this little flirt out of your
sight for one second
and she starts shopping for a new papa.
If you can't be a responsible pet owner,
then maybe you don't
deserve this little unicorn.
Guilty on all charges, your honor.
Shant happen again.
Why are you so nice?
It costs nothing to be kind.
Shutting the fuck up is also free.
Caliente.
This is Logan.
He's usually shirtless,
but he's let himself go
since the divorce.
Where's your mask?
Come on, guys.
Oh, this guy.
We're looking for a group of survivors.
Oh, they're out there.
Yeah.
But Merc to Merc, you better hope
that you don't run
into the Deadpool corps.
Yeah, they're crazy.
They will chop you up
into a thousand pieces
and hide you all over the void.
If they could only
process their childhood trauma,
they'd go on one heck
of a healing journey.
Look, we're headed for the borderlands.
Do you know where it is?
Borderlands, yeah, that's 12 clicks.
Due West, I can lend you
my ride if you like.
It would be my honor.
(wind rustling)
Oh, no, no, no, no,
no, no, absolutely not.
Nuh-uh, what the?
No, no.
Just get in the car.
This isn't a car.
This is a Honda fucking Odyssey.
Throttle response sucks a cock.
Dated infotainment system.
When Honda saw that untreated chlamydia
was making a comeback, they
invented the Honda Odyssey
to compete.
Get in the fucking car.
He'll get you there safe and sound.
Old Betsy always does.
You're gonna have to
give me my dog back though.
I know, listen.
Yes child.
If you ever wanna give her up,
or if she needs a new home,
or if something should happen to you,
I'd love to be her papa.
Oh, what would ever happen to me?
Lots of stuff.
No, we're running away.
Don't, the corn was too dense, girl.
Fuck.
(car door slams)
Won't somebody come take me home?
It's a damn cold night
Trying to figure out
This life
Won't you take me by the hand?
Take me somewhere new
I don't know who you are
But I
I'm with you
Okay, I'm just gonna ask it.
What's with the suit?
First thing I did when I flamed out,
I took mine off.
Drop it.
It's not that ugly.
Stop talking about myself.
Did you make it yourself?
Been there.
Quit now.
The X-Men make you wear it?
Those sons of fucking bitches.
They are not your
friends, I'll tell you that.
Friends don't let friends leave the house
looking like they fight
crime for the Los Angeles Rams.
Shut the fuck up about the suit.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Watch your frown lines, angel baby.
I'm just trying to bond a little bit.
Yeah, well then talk
about something else.
Fine.
(Spider Man web slinger sounds)
Stop it.
If they can fix your world.
What's the first thing you're gonna do
when you get out of here?
Some rubbing alcohol shots?
Maybe a wiper fluid chaser?
What did you say?
So when you get back,
what's the first thing you're gonna do?
No, no, no, before that.
IF they can fix your world?
(car brakes)
(tires screetch)
What do you mean if. I mean--
You lied to me.
You don't have a fucking clue if
they can help me fix things,
do you?
No, I mean--
Oh, fuck!
Fuck!
I didn't lie.
You lied.
No, I made an educated wish.
Because I need you.
This, this is why.
Right here.
Because if we don't
do something, they die.
I don't know anything
about saving worlds.
And why would I even care?
Because my entire world is
right here in this picture.
It's only nine people,
and I have no idea how to save it alone.
I know how to fuck people up for money,
but you, you, know how to save them.
At least other Wolverine did.
Oh, fuck!
I guess I'm stuck with the worst one.
Did you say you made an
educated fucking wish?
They call me the Merc with the Mouth.
They don't call me Truthful Timmy,
the blowjob queen of Saskatoon.
(claws retracting)
Agh!
One more word.
Please give me one.
Gubernatorial.
(screams)
You know what, you're a fucking joke.
No wonder the Avengers didn't take you.
Or the X-Men, they'll
take fucking anyone.
I mean, you are a
ridiculous, immature, half-wit moron.
I have never met a
sadder, more attention-starved,
jabbering little prick in my entire life.
And that says a lot,
because I've been alive
for more than 200 fucking years.
I'll tell ya, that bald
chick was right about one thing.
You will never save the world.
You couldn't even save a relationship
with a goddamn stripper.
And motherfucker, I wish I
could say you die alone,
but it's one of God's best
jokes that you can't die,
except that's on all of us.
(panting)
You got nothing to say, mouth?
I'm gonna fight you now.
Oh, are you?
(grunts)
(radio starts playing)
Oh you
Not talking now are ya?
(grunts)
Ow you dirty, bitch!
(screams)
(grunts)
(glass shattering)
No, no, no.
(screams)
(grunts)
Nice.
I take it all back, the
Honda Odyssey fucks hard.
Too bad you don't needle dick.
Oh, we're just getting started, bub.
(screams)
(music plays)
(engine revs)
Thor!
Where are we?
No clue, but I like it here.
(sword clang)
Whoa whoa whoa!
(dramatic music)
Okay, look at you, all.
You must be the others.
Terrific.
So just to refresh, you are one--
Electra. Electra, yes.
Who could forget?
And you, I was not
expecting to see you here,
thought you were, you know, retired.
Retarded?
Retired.
I'm already in the void.
I'm not trying to get canceled again.
I don't like you.
You never did.
And who's this succulent
reminder of my own inadequacies?
Look at you.
You look like the
superhero version of Hawkeye.
The name's Remy LeBeau.
Le Diable Blanc (The White Devil)
but you can call me the Gambit.
It's been a while
since I've seen Sling Blade
hit me again.
They call me the Gambit.
Do they?
Are you sure you didn't just really,
really want them to,
but it never quite worked out?
Bon de rien (Good for nothing)
You know, we never had
a Wolverine up in here.
But I can tell you now, it's just a
common courtesy to ask
before you drink up all of my liquor.
That's a good thing I don't give a fuck.
(chuckles)
Couillon, va! (You dumbass!)
(glass shattering) Fuck!
So embarrassing.
Well, now that that's settled,
look, we came a long
way to find you three.
There's four of us.
There's four?
Wait, is it Magneto?
Dear sweet God in
heaven, let it be Magneto,
because with him- He's dead.
Fuck!
Now Disney gets cheap?
It's like Pinocchio
jammed his face in my ass
and started lying like crazy.
Ohh you nasty (jabbering in Cajun) huh?
Not a single word,
what do you do exactly?
Charge the playing cards.
Make them go boom.
Your power's close
up magic, that's good.
We're not totally fucked at all.
So who brought us here?
That would be me.
(somber music)
Don't make me regret it.
Holy shit, Logan,
that's her, that's X-23.
She's the one they told you about.
How did you all get stuck in the void?
There was a knock at the door,
TVA sent me here.
Me too.
Maybe I was born here, so
it's hard to know for sure.
TVA decided our universe was dying,
and I never even got a
chance to fight for it.
People like us don't go quietly.
TVA knows that, so they took us out.
The answer is yes, I'm in.
In what?
A team.
Me, you, you and me, all of us together.
Let's get the fuck out of this place.
Don't listen to him, he's a fucking liar
It was an educated wish!
Ha! Look.
We've been inside Cassandra's lair.
The only way out of
the void is through her.
She can get us home.
She told us.
Wait a minute, you've been inside?
And you made it out alive?
Bullshit.
Nobody's ever done that.
We did.
Every time one of us
is going up against her,
they die.
The Punisher, the
Quicksilver, the Daredevil.
Daredevil, I'm so sorry.
It's fine.
Okay.
Even that sweet baby angel, Johnny Storm,
he up and going missing
like, what, two days ago?
Ah, that's so sad.
Wherever this Johnny fella
is, I'm sure he's thriving.
Look, there's strength
in numbers, all right?
Us, plus you guys, we can
put Cassandra over our knee
and force her to let us out of the void.
I know what it means to feel self-doubt.
I don't feel that at all.
I'm good.
Know how you get your gut like
a coked up tape worm.
It's like you're holding up
a mirror to my soul.
You guys may not have been
able to save your universes,
but you can avenge them.
It's what Johnny would have wanted.
Wait, you knew Johnny?
Oh yeah.
Dickhead here, talk to
him, and we'll team up.
When Johnny came down with
a little case of the dead.
No, no, no, no, we don't know that.
It was just a flesh wound.
He may have survived.
If he survived that,
he is praying for death.
Thank you, Dr. Wolverine.
Spill it!
What you do to Johnny, huh?
Talk or I'm gonna start dealing.
Okay, okay, hey, hey, hey.
Okay, he ran his fatass
mouth about Cassandra,
and she zip-zapped his skin,
leaving his organs to
splash crudely onto the ground
while the soil greedily drank his blood.
It was horrible.
He was like a brother to me.
Look, he died before he
could make a difference,
but maybe you couldn't save your world,
but Jesus Christ, you could save mine.
I don't give a shit about your world,
but if these two made
it out of there alive,
maybe together, we could
get back in and take her down.
Where I come from?
We call that suicide, cher.
If we can block her psychic powers,
we can get a leg up.
I know it.
Now, I know Magneto's dead,
but I venture to guess that his helmet
is lying around here somewhere.
Cassandra melted that helmet. Fuck!
After she killed him. Fuck!
She don't blink.
She knows that helmet was the only way
to protect anyone from her powers.
The only other helmet
that strong is Juggernauts,
but he works for Cassandra.
Juggernauts helmet, that's it.
And we don't be knowing
that lid ain't coming off.
Without that dome gonna come out with it.
I'm so sorry, beautiful,
I want this to be gentle
Who is your dialect coach?
The Minions?
I feel like we're missing
critical exposition here.
I'm sick of this shit.
I'm sick of hiding.
Let's face it, our
world's forgot about us.
Or, never learned about us.
The heroes we were.
Lives we saved.  Or wanted to save.
Maybe these two are our chance,
(gurgling)
to be remembered the way we deserve.
Yes. An ending.
Legacy.
Yes, yes, let this man cook.
This is what I'm talking about.
Big slow motion, fight. Sad music,
everybody working together.
Who knows if you live or
die, that sort of thing.
Who's ready?
I was born ready.
Yes, Gambit!
I ain't know my daddy,
but I'm sure I shot
out of his dick ready.
Jesus Christ, that is graphic.
Yeah, he was laying them buttery nuts
all up in my mama
and I shot out there and
I said, "What's up, doc?"
Johnny must've loved you.
X-23, what's it gonna be?
The name's Laura.
Let's fucking go.
So, let's kick it and go.
Yeah, we're doing this.
You're all fucking dead.
My god, read the room.
Hey hey I'm not looking for company.
Get out of here.
You remind me of him.  Angry, drunk, mean.
Sounds like a great guy.
I wasn't finished.
Showed up when it mattered the most.
Couldn't help it.
You might not know it, but
you're a good man, Logan.
apparently I'm the worst,
Logan.
I got to have a life because of you.
I got to grow up because of you.
A lot of kids didn't.
A lot of kids didn't
grow up because of me.
Trust me, kid, I'm no hero.
That suit says different.
Yeah?
What do you like it?
Scott used to beg me to wear it.
So did Jean, Storm, Beast.
All of them.
Wanted me to be part of the team but I didn't
Told them they all
looked fucking ridiculous.
I couldn't have them
thinking I wanted to be there.
And then one day,
while I was off on my own,
the humans came.
And went mutant hunting.
I can guess the rest.
No, no, let me.
Let me say it.
I need to say it.
By the time I stumbled
shit faced from the bar,
it was too late.
They were dead, every...
(dramatic music)
This suit's all I got to
remind me of who they were.
And what I did.
We're headed to Cassandra's at sun up.
Have fun, not my fight.
We won't pull this off without you.
Hey, whoever you think I am
you got the wrong guy.
You were always the wrong guy.
(dramatic music)
What?
Alioth didn't get them.
Cassandra wanted to play
with them herself first.
They got away.
Did they find the others?
No.
Good, all right, phew.
The others found them.
Oh, very cute, well done, Pyro.
Classic bait and switch
you really got me there.
Relax.
They come after Nova, she'll handle it.
Cassandra is a lunatic wild card.
Why do you think we put
her there in the first place?
Thank God she's never
chosen to leave the void.
The time ripper is
hours away from completion.
I cannot take any chances.
Maybe not, but I can.
For a price.
Why do you have to say
it, in that silly voice?
It's so icky.
You want it done or not?
All right, your price, take her out.
Ugh Mutants.
Woo!
Bring them out, bring them out
It's hard to yell when
when the barrel's in ya mouth
Come on
Bring them out, bring them out
Hey Bring them out, bring them out
TIP, coming live
from the VIP
Heard the night light
life lost life without me
Both the Feds and the State wanna see 'bout me
The whole city got biz-zerk, he got three
Woo look at that, there.
See them big'em hands come close?
They not a want
an up inside there.
What Gambit's trying to say
is getting Juggernaut's helmet
ain't gonna be easy.
I'm just making stuff up with this.
Yeah, tilt up to Blade.
Gun!
This is
Mississippi to Philly,
Albuquerque to Chatt Town
If I hit you in the face
you gon' be suin' and shit
Where do you get that little beauty?
That's the Punisher's AT4.
Which Punisher?
There's been like five of them.
There's only been one Blade.
There's only ever gonna be one Blade.
Who got a flow and a live
show better than mine
I got a packed house yellin'
Incoming!
Bring them out, bring them out
(dramatic fire whooshing)
(tire screetching)
(car hatch opening)
(footstep)
(dramatic music)
Oh, this is gonna be good.
You know how long I've
been waiting for this?
Whoo, I'm about to make
a name for myself here.
I don't think you
guys walk away from this.
You just make sure people know what
happened here today.
When you get out of here,
you have a drink for me, yeah?
You'll stay on our six and get inside.
We'll make sure you get the package.
And we'll get our ending.
(dramatic music)
(screaming)
A boom!
Some motherfucker's still
trying to ice skate up here.
(screaming)
You two escaping I could live with,
but coming back, willingly.
Boys are so silly.
I just need to get home.
Well, that's not on the menu, I'm afraid.
It's death or
enslavement, a la carte, of course.
Up you go--
(screaming)
Finally, it's nice to give
someone else a chance to talk.
Not my strong suit.
(screaming)
You shouldn't have done that.
Adios, pendejo.
(screaming)
You are an interesting one, aren't you?
I do feel like you get
lost behind all of his.
(humming)
Deadpools are a dime a
dozen here in the void.
But you, what's going on in here?
(growling)
(silence)
Interesting.
Not what I expected back here
Behind the anger
You're hiding, from them,
from all the ones you let down.
So much pain.
I walked away.
They called after me and I walked away.
I always do.
I know.
That's not all you did, is it?
(growling)
You found them, the X-Men?
Dead.
Dead
But I would.
What did you do?
I started killing and I couldn't stop.
I didn't want to stop.
All those bad men.
It's not just the bad ones.
My little animal.
I turned the whole
world against the X-Men.
Just once.
I want to be the man
that Charles thought I was.
Logan, in the void you
can be all that you are.
I just want to be free.
I can set you free.
I can silence all those voices. I've got you.
I've got you.
No, I got you.
(screaming) Get it off!
You're gonna send us home
or I'm gonna twist
your fucking head off.
Why are you laughing?
I can't send you home unless you
get this thing off my head.
And as soon as you do that,
I'm going to boil your
brains on an atomic level
whilst flicking my bean
to the Enya box set.
There's an Enya box set?
Either you kill me or I kill you.
Both wonderful options.
You want me to do it?
No, I'll do it.
I have her neck right
here, it's really no problem.
You'll screw it up.
Oh come on, Mr. PG-13
except the last one.
What the fuck?
No, no, no.
You have no idea what it's like.
Day after day, shovel the shit.
Fetch the meats.
I have spent my entire
Exist-
Not everyone gets a speech.
She's gonna die.
Okay, hey, hey, if I
take this helmet off,
you promise you won't kill us.
I promise I will kill you first.
Why are you like this?
I wish I knew.
Take it off.
What?
Why?
Just take it off.
This is our only chance to fix our shit.
Take it off!
I am wearing the suit.
And that means a lot of things,
but most of all, it means I'm an X-Man.
And I know your brother.
As much as I'm wanna fucking kill you,
every bone in my body
wants to fucking kill you.
He would not let me
stand here and watch you die.
Take your hands off.
This is for him.
This is for Charles.
(dramatic music)
No no no, don't you dare do me like Johnny.
My brother loved you.
He loved all of us.
Hmm. Must be nice.
He would have loved you too.
If he knew about you,
if he knew where you were,
he would have torn a
hole in the fucking universe
to bring you home.
This is my home.
Then at least let us save his.
...
You wanna hear something crazy?
An amateur magician
rolled through here
a while back.
I killed him, of course,
wore his skin around for four days.
But I found this little trinket
on his lovely fingers.
Strange.
Marvel sparkle circle.
What is that?
This is your way home.
I do owe you for saving my life,
but let's keep things interesting.
I'd say you have about four seconds
before your life's through.
Ha ha ha race you.
I'll be seeing you
In all the old familiar
Places
That this heart of mine
Embraces
All day through
In that small cafe
The park across the way
The children's carousel
The chestnut trees
the wishing well
I'll be seeing you
In every lovely summer's day
I'll find you in the morning sun
And when the night is new
I'll be looking at the moon
But I'll be seeing you
As I guess, we got a standard three year
bumper to bumper warranty.
Glad you gave us a second chance.
And don't worry, Wade and I are a team,
so I'll see you again after--
(loud thuds)
That feels like a
Kia, Kia fucking carnival wasn't it?
Oh.
Holy shit, that's Deadpool.
That's Wolverine.
You damn straight it is.
Fox killed him.
Disney brought him back.
They're gonna make him
do this till he's 90.
Let's go.
I'll clock you out.
Forever.
Wakey wakey.
Hey.
Now you put all these bullets in my belly
and I'm gonna find out why.
Whoa, whoa!
I'll just say it
You don't have to
stick your fingers in me.
Jesus, just ask sometimes.
Fine.
Really?
Hands and pockets.
A guy named Paradox.
He said he'd get me out of the void.
All I know is he works for the TVA.
The TVA?
We had an agreement.
I don't.
think this guy cares.
Huh, he will.
Hey people, how much longer
before the time ripper is active?
We're running the final safety checks.
Oh, okay, all right,
thanks for all your hard work,
Ralph, nice job.
Really?
No, you drooling boob.
No, we have company,
cancel the safety checks.
We need to be live now.
Oh, I hate you so much.
No, stop, piss off, you're too late.
You're fucking done.
Why was Thor more crying.
How dare you?
No one comes back from the void.
Tell that to Cassandra Nova.
Paradox, we have a problem.
Paradox?
Well you are doughier than
you looked in Pyro's head,
You tried to kill me.
I literally have no idea.
When you come for the king, you better kill the king.
Oh, welcome to the
skull fuck club, Paradox.
You know she doesn't wash that hand.
Oh, what's this?
A time ripper, naughty boy.
Oh no, we're on it, we're gonna head down
and dismantle that thing now.
We got you, boo, you just
keep playing those keys.
I don't want to destroy it.
I want to use it.
Now shoo, mommy and daddy
are having a conversation.
(screaming)
You know the funny thing is?
I was happy in the void.
You sent the trash to me,
while I cleaned it up.
Everyone was happy.
And you had to go and
piss on my side of the fence.
And so now the fence must come down.
I'm going to use a little time ripper
and I'm going to destroy this universe
and the next and the next and the next
until all that's left is the void.
And I get to play God.
Come on.
Now, who are going to show me how to use
this fancy gadget of yours?
And don't worry, I've called some friends
and to make sure we're not disturbed.
Sorry to bother, madam,
but there's something you need to see.
We're getting indications of an
unsanctioned time ripper
activating on Earth 10005.
Whose district is that?
Paradox.
Well, thank you so much
for your help, darling.
God, good to get out of that head.
Wooo what a mess.
Stop.
Let's give it a beat
for the extras to clear.
Go, go, go, go.
Oh my God.
(music starts playing)
It's her.
Santa perrita.
Come on, girl.
My girl, we don't have to
be a apart, ever again.
Never, ever again.
Sorry.
Fuck!
What's cafe gratitude doing here?
Sorry about that.
Tremble not, sweet Mary Puppins.
Oh, that's a little...
Come here, girl.
Papa is here.
Hey, do not insult
this animal's autonomy.
She can decide who her papa is.
What's it gonna be, girl, huh?
Original recipe?
Or Van Milder here.
Oh, that's funny.
I can gently tap the fourth wall too.
The Proposal.
The fuck was that?
Bitch, you think that's what I do?
Both of you, shut up.
You smell something?
Yeah, you.
A lot of you.
Told you there were a lot
of Deadpools over there?
That's bad.
I take it they're not friendly.
Goodness, no.
Sorry about this, boys.
Mission over.
Cause of death, 100.
Kill thirsty Deadpools.
They're dumb, but they can fight.
Not me though.
I'd love to get in the mix,
but I have low bone density
and I have to keep my face safe.
Hold please.
Oh, okay.
All right, look.
Guys!
Deadpool Prime here.
Our fight isn't with you.
Hey, when I want your opinions,
I'll take Wolverine's
dick out of your mouth.
That's Kidpool, she's the dirtiest.
Can we just be done?
Ooh, we're just getting started.
No, no, no, no, no.
With the whole multiverse thing.
It's not great.
It's just been miss
after miss after miss.
Look, the Wizard of Oz did the multiverse first
and they did it best.
The gays knew it, but we didn't listen.
Let's just take the L and move on.
I think it's been
steadily great since Endgame.
What are you talking about?
The multiverse is over.
Cassandy gonna destroy the
fuck out of every timeline.
Heh, ya'll can't do shit about it.
Do you not get it?
If we don't go down to
the subway and stop her
we all die.
Say the boss lady
don't want no disturbance.
You wanna get down to the subway?
You gotta go through us
Uzi time, baby.
Look alive.
(gun fires)
I think I'm hit.
No shit, you did that on purpose.
I did no such thing.
Listen to me, gorgeous.
How long does it take
for you to regenerate?
Regenerate?
You really are God's
perfect idiot, aren't you?
I'm okay.
How dare you, you
insensitive son of a bitch.
How was I supposed to
know he doesn't regenerate?
I'm not a medicine woman.
Look, a donut cart.
They're practically hospitals.
They sell portable triage units.
They don't.
I'm gonna get you to safety.
He's not.
Deep breath.
(gunshots)
(dartgun blows)
Hey, why are we stopping?
Just catching my breath.
Are your legs on vacation?
You're dead weight.
It's because I'm paralyzed.
We all have problems.
Listen to me.
You're gonna live.
Look at me, Nicepool.
Say it.
I'm gonna live.
Say it with me.
You're gonna live.
I'm gonna-I'm gonna live.
Ha ha.
Say it louder.
I'm gonna live!
Hold your fire!
Sweet little puppy.
Goddamit!
I don't think he's gonna make it.
God, he loved his face.
I could taste his final thought.
He was so afraid.
But he died a hero.
He died from murder, you dumb fuck.
All I have to remember him by
are these two gold-plated,
50 caliber desert eagle pistoleros.
This is for him.
Are you ready?
I get to kill 100 yous.
Fuck yeah, I'm ready.
You don't wanna see this, bub.
That's a good girl.
(dramatic music)
Life is a mystery
Everyone must stand alone
I hear you call my name
And it feels like
Home
(dramatic music)
Holy shit.
You saved the good
stuff for special occasions?
Killing mostly.
What's the wind resistance
on those blowjob handles?
Sorry, just a catty
bitch when I'm jealous.
All right, let's do this.
Maximum effort.
(dramatic music)
(wind blowing)
When you call my name
it's like a little prayer
I'm down on my knees
I wanna take you there
In the midnight hour
I can feel your power
Just like a prayer
you know I'll take you there
Life is a mystery
Everyone must stand alone
(dramatic music)
I'm down on my knees
I wanna take you there
Motherfucker?
I wish I were deaf.
(dramatic music)
(It's like a dream to me) oh yeah, oh yeah yeah yeah yeah
(Just like a prayer, I'll take you there) oh yeah yeah yee
(It's like a dream to me) whoa oh-oh
(gunshots)
(screams)
(glass shattering)
(dramatic music) (crashing)
Come on, I blew it.
After all that, the only
thing you're gonna remember
is that god-awful dismount.
(baby cooing)
What are you laughing at, ya little fucker?
Oh no.
I guess these ones regenerate.
Come on, we don't have time for this.
Deadpools, stand down.
(dramatic music)
(crashing)
This Deadpool's with me.
Oh no.
Holy shit.
That's fucking Peter.
(screaming)
Wait, you guys know Peter?
Are you kidding me?
Every Deadpool has a Peter.
Shit, Peter's a goddamn legend
in every Deadpool's world.
Peter-san.
Hai
(dramatic music)
Enjoy my Peter.
(crashing)
Oh, now you're here.
Oh well, you're too late, it's all over.
Not yet, it's not.
No, no, no, no, but we're very close.
Homestretch, folks, promise.
Quick, let's up the stakes.
If she steals the time ripper then,
she has the power to shred
the fabric of all the realities
until there is nothing left but the void.
How do we shut it down?
I don't know.
How about now?
The mask is really intimidating, huh?
It's like Batman
except he can move his neck.
Okay, look, look, look, look, look.
(crashing)
The ripper is fed from a
secure chamber below ground.
It is powered by twin
matter and antimatter feeds
converging inside the device.
Now Cassandra Nova is
redirecting the ripper's power
to eliminate all
timelines, starting with this one.
Theoretically, you could stop her
by short circuiting the
feeds in the chamber below.
One of you would create a
circuit between the two feeds,
then the released power
would destroy the machine.
But, well- Come on, man!
If you're not gonna swallow, spit it out.
Whoever formed the
bridge would be annihilated.
I could live with that.
I could live with that too, actually.
You know, we survive anything.
We're like cockroaches he he he.
Not this time.
This is matter and antimatter.
They do not play nicely with each other.
When they mix in your
body, you will be atomized.
Trust the laws of
physics if you don't trust me.
Even if you lived long
enough to make the circuit,
you will die down there.
(dramatic music)
(electric pulsing)
Hold up, hold it.
You heard that asshole upstairs.
Even if we pull this off,
we're dead, permanently.
That's why it's gotta be me.
What?
Look, man, you didn't
ask for any of this.
You were right.
I lied.
I lied right to your face.
Just to get you to help me, you did.
You didn't lie.
You made an educated wish.
Come on.
You got a whole world to go back to.
I got nothing.
Give me this.
Hey.
(dramatic music)
I waited a long time for this team up.
You know something?
You're the best Wolverine.
Say hi to your friends for me.
(dramatic music)
Open the door.
I can't hear you over all
the noble sacrifice.
Why are you fucking doing this?
Because I'm Marvel Jesus.
Or Spock.
Hard to say.
Wade!
You fucking idiot.
(laughs)
Sorry, I'm just stalling.
I think I'm nervous about dying.
It should be me.
Say hi to my friends for me, Peanut.
Wade.
Way to be annoying prick,
You'll be sorry.
You're not gonna die again, you dumb fuck.
(dramatic music)
Wade, you don't need to do this.
I'm not doing it because I need it.
I'm doing it because they do.
(dramatic music)
No!
(crashing sound)
All right.
(dramatic music)
He's not gonna make it.
(door bashing)
(dramatic music)
It's over.
(dramatic drum beats)
("Like a Prayer" plays)
(dramatic music)
The Wolverine is a hero in my world.
Whoever you think I am,
you got the wrong guy.
You were always the wrong guy.
Till you weren't.
(dramatic music)
Wade.
Wade, you can finally, finally, matter.
(dramatic music)
Vanessa. I wanna see Vanessa.
For the first time in
my life, I am proud.
To wear this suit.
It means I'm an X-man.
I am the X-man.
(dramatic music)
(somber music)
Paradox.
You've been busy.
Well, somebody has been.
We had some strange
readings from this location.
You wouldn't know anything about an
unsanctioned time ripper,
would you?
No, no, I wouldn't know anything
about an unsanctioned time ripper.
Maybe you should ask Cassandra Nova,
because I was assured that
she was safely held in the void.
But no, she was here
and she fondled my brain.
How did you let this happen?
You weren't involved at all.
In stopping her, yes, yes, I was.
But not nearly enough.
Not as much as the men who
went down there after her.
My men, my friends,
I warned them, but they would be
completely obliterated
if they went, but they went anyway, like,
like heroes.
Because that's who they were.
They just did what they had to do.
With no concern for their own safety.
The fact that we are
all still standing here
is a testament to their heroism.
Anyway, there's nothing you or I can do
to bring them back now.
He has risen baby girl
Fuck!
And I don't want the world to see me
Cause I don't think
that they'd understand
When everything's made to be broken
I just want you to know who I am
Found your new anchor being.
And we're doing just
fine you piece of shit.
Mm mm mm, fine indeed.
All right, put your greasy
tits away, you preening slut.
I don't understand.
How are you two still alive?
You're right, one of us
would have been killed.
But you put a Deadpool
and a Wolverine together,
make them hold hands
while listening to Madonna?
Indestructible motherfucker.
Let's get this Deadpool
variant back to the void.
Wait, hold on, what?
Nope, actually, this one's homegrown.
Like me, he belongs here.
And you are?
Peter Pool.
But you can call me Peter.
And I hope that you do.
What the fuck is happening here?
You are under judgment
for operating an
unsanctioned time-ripper.
Take'em.
I was just doing what you
don't have the guts to do.
Get off, get off, your
insolent hands off me.
I'm grateful, gentlemen.
Let's hold the bows.
You led an Omega level
mutant to this timeline.
You're welcome.
And you shouldn't even
be near this timeline.
He's welcome.
And you look damn good in that suit.
I'm so sorry.
(beeping)
I wanna show you something.
Something huge.
That's what
Scoutmaster Kevin used to say.
Do you see that?
Your universe is regenerating.
Whatever you did here, you
not only saved your world,
you spared your timeline from extinction.
I'd rest up.
I have a feeling your work
is only just getting started.
Till you're 90.
Wait!
We couldn't have made it out of the void
without some help from some people
that the world kinda forgot.
Is there any way that
you could maybe find a way
to bring them home?
I'll see what I can do.
And I promised my friend here
that the TVA could undo
some pretty awful shit
in his timeline.
What would you say to that?
Change the past?
He did help me save the world.
And his past made him the man who did it.
There's nothing to fix, Mr. Wilson.
Logan.
Shawarma?  I could eat yeah.
You know the Avengers discovered Shawarma.
They'd be lucky to have you.
(dog barking)
Ohhhh
Fuck off!
Come here my little cuntshkin,
Yes it's you, you're a survivor.
Look, all is right in the world.
Yes it is.
So what are you gonna do next?
I'll figure it out.
I always do.
All right.
Well I'll probably see you around.
Probably not.
See you, bub.
Logan!
Al, I'm back.
About damn time, you holding?
I'm all out of devil's dandruff
and I'm shaking like an angry vibrator.
Thank you, Al.
We have company.
Althea, this is Logan.
Nice to meet you, Logan.
Nice to meet you too.
And this little ancient,
anal shit-knot is Mary Puppins.
Or as I like to call her, Dogpool.
You wanna treat
yourself to a little stroke?
Get the tongue.
Oh my God, motherfucker!
Right, it's like an
armadillo fucked a gremlin,
angrily, in a bed of gonorrhea,
and didn't stop till the sun came up.
Everyone wants to matter.
Turns out that you don't need to be
Marvel Jesus to do it.
You just need to open
your eyes and look around.
And if you're lucky,
you'll find a few friends.
Old friends and some new ones too.
(soulful music)
Give me the fucking
dog, talk to the girl.
(soulful music)
Oh, hi.
Hi.
You've been busy.
I did it for you.
Even if you don't want me, I did it for you.
Turns out, I am the world saving type.
Just look around this
table if you want proof.
And the best part,
sometimes the people we save,
well they save us right back.
("Youre All I Need to Get By" plays)
(Guitar strums)
You are not the only one with gifts.
What is this place?
("Good Riddance" by Green Day plays)
Another turning point
a fork stuck in the road
Time grabs you by the wrist
directs you where to go
So make the best of this test
and don't ask why
It's not a question, but a lesson learned in time
Nice suit.
Zip it Stan Lee.
("Good Riddance" continues playing)
I really like the art
in the Deadpool comics.
You know, I just always
felt kind of a kinship to him.
I just thought, I'd like to play that guy someday.
("Good Riddance" continues playing)
I was there for three weeks
before I shot a single thing.
For that first day of
shooting, I was so nervous, man.
Everyone was sort of
going, who's this guy.
You know, there was a lot of that.
You know, was he going to deliver or not
and you can feel all
that kind of pressure.
Always the suit's fault
Never the actor.
("Good Riddance" continues playing)
(screaming)
This is, the only way.
It's something unpredictable
But in the end, it's right
I hope you had the time of your life
Oh, this is what it feels like.
And there's the lights.
Medical research.
Bye bye, video.
(smootch)
(upbeat music)
I'm tired of these absolutely vile rumors
that I got Johnny killed.
Let's look at the tape.
In the void, you're either food for Alioth
or you work for her.
Go on, Johnny.
And I'll tell you who her is.
Cassandra Nova, a
megalomaniacal psychotic asshole.
A finger-licking dead inside pixie slab
of third rate dime store nut milk.
And I'll tell you what she can do.
I'm listening.
She can lick my
goddamn cinnamon ring clean
and kick rocks all the way to bald hell.
In fact, I don't give a
shit if she removes all my skin
and pops me like some
nightmarish blood balloon.
If the last thing I do
with this, God forsaken,
cum gutter existence,
is light that fuck box on a
fire I still won't die happy.
Holy shit, girl, you crazy.
That's right, Wade.
I won't be happy until I've urinated
on her freshly barbecued corpse
and husk fucked the charred remains
while gargling Juggernuts juggernuts.
Wow.
And you can quote me.
Kay.
Gotcha, fuck face.